

Tagiltsev
SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Address Jihlava 58601

Phone Number +420603889044

Website

https://eugeneslab.net

**Email Address** 

tagiltsev.evgenii@gmail.com

Linkedin

Personal page

GitHub

**Projects** 

#### **SKILLS**

**QML** 

Advanced

C/C++

Intermediate

Linux

administration

Novice

HTML/CSS/JS

Novice

**Qt** Advanced **Git** 

Advanced **REST API** 

REST API MySQL/SQLite
Intermediate Intermediate

React Native

Novice

Android SDK

Novice

Cryptography
Fundamental
Awareness

## LANGUAGES

**Russian** Native English B1

Czech

Αl

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Accomplished software developer with extensive experience of task solving using various programming languages including C++ and C, internet protocols, programming for embedded systems, programming desktop applications with user interfaces, or console applications.

Demonstrated ability to work as a crucial member of a team within the construction department framework of an aviation company. Strong track record of both high-quality assignments, namely producing custom-made devices for customers, in addition to experimental personal projects, such as creating devices controlled by microcontrollers or designing an application for private safe online messaging, currently in progress.

Highly interested in current developments in the ICT and different fields of study. Other hobbies include improvement of English on a daily basis, advancement in personal projects, together with playing computer games and cycling

#### **EDUCATION**

Ural Federal University, Faculty of Foundation education,
Department of Information systems and technologies
Bachelor's Degree Information Technology

(August 2011 -July 2015)

Diploma Thesis: Detecting human movements on video taken from camera

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Experimental department of Ural factory of civil aviation

(November 2014 - May 2019)

Engineer - programmer

- Developing custom-made programs based on customers' requirements
- Developing algorithms for task solving
- Testing and debugging
- Developing sample devices and prototypes to check solved tasks
- Deploying applications to customers' devices
- Supporting, updating, and upgrading applications

#### Demlabs inc.

Qt programmer

(July 2019 - February 2020)

- Developing a GUI application based on prototypes
- Developing a service application for connection with Cellframe Node

## **Redwood Games**

Qt programmer

• Fixing bugs of "Plutocracy" game

## Nexus

Qt/QML Developer

(October 2020 - Present)

(January 2020 - April 2020)

• Developing questionnaire system for education environment

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Avionic of aircraft

Kazan Aircraft University

Document number: 162400319885

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

## Vysočina - the Best Holiday

(June 2020 - February 2021)

Participant and prizewinner: Competition focused on tourism promotion in the Vysočina Region in the CR - awarded as one among the most creative solutions. Developed Routefinder - an app which enables tourists to filter touristic routes in the region according to their preferences - distance, objects, cities, etc. The app offers a wide selection of routes written in its database from which tourists can choose the route most suitable for them achieved

## **Project Eurobot**

(March 2013 - February 2021)

Participant and team prizewinner: An international robotic competition - 3rd place achieved.

# HOBBIES

# Cycling

Computer games

Personal development

Language improvement

Board games